allcinegallery.com 2014-11-23

# Privacy Policy & Disclaimer - Stills Images Photos Posters Wallpapers

**Privacy Policy**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

 **Third Party Advertising**  
Sites like Google AdSense, Google Analytics, FeedBurner or other third-party services may place and read cookies or use web beacons to collect non-personal information. These services use the data to track conversions, to show statistics about this site or to improve their features.

Cookies are small pieces of data that reside on your computer and can only be read by the sites that placed them. You can disable cookies, manually clear them and control which cookies are allowed.

To find more, read Google’s privacy policy, Yahoo’s privacy policy and the privacy policies of the third-party services accepted by Google AdSense.

 **DoubleClick DART cookie**  
Some of our advertising partners as third party may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to serve the advertisements and links that appear on our site and are sent directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

 **Security**  
Allcinegallery.com endeavors to protect the security of your personal information. We do not share your personally identifiable information with other companies, apart from those acting as our agents in providing our service to you, all of which agree to use it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential. However, if you find any unsuitable link / advertisement, then please contact us giving detail of such links.

 **Disclaimer**  
Some images contained in allcinegallery.com have been obtained from various internet sources. The copyright of these pictures belongs to their original publisher / photographer. Please let us know at if any Copyright Violation occurs and we will remove them right away. If by anyhow any of the content is offensive to you, please, contact us asking for the removal. If you own copyrights over any of them and do not agree with it being shown here, please send us an email with ownership proof and we will remove it. email us at admin@allcinegallery.com

Any links provided or advertisements displayed on our site are for informational purposes only and We are not responsible for any damages or consequences. However, if you find any unsuitable link / advertisement, then please contact us giving detail of such links etc.

 **Contact Information:**  
If you have any questions please contact – admin@allcinegallery.com
